反恐24小时
第九季 第4集
前情提要
武器系统
我的無人機被什麼控制了！
Something's taken control of my drone!
導彈已被裝填準備發射！
It's armed the missile to attack!
-=TLF字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
找掩護！
Get to cover now!
長官，快躲開，快躲開！
Sir, move! Move!
不！不！
No! No!
翻译  筱宸葭
有鑒於今早的不幸事件
In light of this morning's unfortunate events
目标已摧毁
海勒總統想要講幾句話
president Heller would like to offer some words.
女士們，先生們
Ladies and gentlemen.
总统  詹姆斯·海勒
翻译  lady5bird
你對今早的事件有何舉措？
What are you going to do about today's incident?
我希望有所言論來解釋所發生
I wish there were words that could explain what
當然有言論
There are words.
翻译  不再的年华
這是謀殺
It was murder.
你連自己的士兵和武器都管不了！
You can't control your soldiers or your weapons!
耶茨設計了一種可控十架
Yates designed an override device
美國無人機的遙控設備
that can take control of as many as ten U.S. drones.
翻译  lydia萌
杰克·鲍尔
這個設備，現在在一已知恐怖分子手上
That device is now in the hands of a known terrorist.
這些新型無人機搭載六枚地獄火導彈
The new drones carry six hellfire missiles.
翻译  LordVader
你知道這能對倫敦這樣的城市造成多大影響嗎？
You have any idea what that could do to a city like London?
國際刑事警察組織人員
Looks like interpol
好像對她臉部做了定位
has a facial-rec match.
克罗伊·奥布赖恩
找到她了
We got her.
西蒙娜·阿爾哈拉茲
Simone Al-Harazi.
校对  LordVader
歐盟多次通緝的恐怖分子
Multiple EU warrants on terrorism-related charges.
她和瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲有關係嗎？
Is she related to Margot Al-Harazi?
有，怎麼了？
Yes. Why?
因為她曾向伊拉克的軍人住宅區
Because she was responsible for an attack
特效  筱宸葭
發動過一次襲擊
on a military housing complex in Iraq.
大多數遇難者是婦女和兒童
Most of the victims were women and children.
西蒙娜是她女兒
Well, Simone is her daughter.
殺人取命可不是小事
It's no small thing to kill a man.
西蒙娜·阿尔哈拉兹
眼睜睜看著他死去
To see the life go out of him.
我覺得我做不出這種事
I didn't think I could do it.
但我做了，你也會如此
But I did. And so will you.
因為我們所做的一切都是必要而公正的
Because what we're doing is necessary and just.
我們置身於戰爭，納維德
We are fighting a war, Naveed.
玛戈·阿尔哈拉兹
最重要的
All that matters
是勝利
is winning.
無人機的操控員叫坦納
The drone pilot's name is Tanner.
黑客组织
新聞裏一直在說
It's all over the news.
评估报告
他正被移交到英國方面
Tanner's about to arrive at the U.S. embassy in London
進行調查
where the handover will take place.
給我創建身份
I'm gonna need you to build me an identity.
高級權限
High-level clearance.
加入大使館來訪登記
Enter it into the visitor's log at the embassy.
要多久做好？
How quickly can you get that done?
證件有問題
The I.D.'s not working.
快離開，傑克，快
Get out, Jack. Get out of there now.
不行，我必須進入大使館
I can't. I have to get into the embassy.
他們在朝我們開槍！他們在朝我們開槍！
They're shooting at us! They're shooting at us!
鮑爾！
Bauer!
以下事件发生在
下午14:00 至下午15:00 之间
基弗·萨瑟兰
反對無人機！反對無人機！
No more drones! No more drones!
伊冯娜
斯特拉霍夫
反對無人機！反對無人機！
No more drones! No more drones!
反對無人機！
No more drones!
泰特·多诺万
克羅伊，我進入大使館了
Chloe, I'm inside the embassy.
怎麼進去的？怎麼回事？
How? What's going on?
我製造意外轉移了他們的注意力
I've created a diversion.
玛丽·莱恩
莱杰斯库
真是輕描淡寫啊
Bit of an understatement.
有個問題，凱特特工
We've got a problem. Agent Morgan
和她的搭檔看到我了
and her partner saw me outside.
他們怎麼知道的？
How did they manage to do that?
威廉·德韦恩
我不清楚，她很有一套
I'm not sure. She's good.
我得盡快進去把飛行密鑰拿到手
I got to get in and out of here with the flight key
然後離開
as quickly as possible.
等等
Hold on.
格本加
阿金纳格贝
贾尔斯
马特蒂
我該怎麼走？
Where am I going?
他們把坦納關在二樓
They're keeping Tanner on the second floor
迈克尔·温科特
東面，217房間
east wing, room 217.
你需要通行證
You're gonna need an access pass
拿到了
I got one.
本杰明·布拉特
如果切爾把他進入大使館的證件資料做好
This wouldn't have happened if chell didn't screw up
事情就不會這樣了
his I.D. At the gate.
你是故意的吧？
You wanted this to happen,didn't you?
基姆·瑞弗
是誰引他來這的？
And who brought him in here?
我只想他遠離我們
I just want him out.
會死人的，你希望這樣嗎？
People are gonna die. Is that what you want?
那誰該為此負責呢？
And who would be responsible for that?
嗯？
Hmm?
客 串
米歇尔·费尔利
我冒著失去生命和自由的危險
I put this group together
科林·萨尔蒙
约翰·波耶加
把各位召集在一起
at some risk to life and liberty
我們是來揭露政府的，而不是協助他們
all of us here to expose governments,not to assist them
埃米莉·伯林顿
利亚姆·加里根
解決他們創造的無人機引發的危機
With the crises they've created by putting drones in the skies.
我不想看到你
Get out of my sight.
萨夏·达万
乔瑟夫·米尔森
米兰达·雷森
斯蒂芬·弗雷
你怎麼幫傑克脫離險境？
How will you get Jack out of there?
剪 辑
斯科特·鲍威尔
我進入了大使館的視頻監控系統
I'm in the embassy security camera system.
艺术指导
乔纳森·李
我規劃了線路圖
I've got a building schematic.
我會救出他的
I'm gonna talk him out.
那裏全是美國海軍陸戰隊
The building is full of U.S. marines.
摄 影
杰弗里 C·麦咖特
我沒說救他會很容易
I didn't say it was gonna be easy.
但我會竭盡所能
But I'm gonna do everything I can.
音 乐
肖恩·卡勒里
我欠他的
I owe Jack.
要不是他我早沒命了
I wouldn't be alive if it weren't for him.
看來我們有共同點了
Then we have that in common.
應該慶幸
Your friend is
我們還需要你朋友的幫助
lucky we still might need his help.
艾德裏安只是做了他認為對的事
Adrian was just doing what he thought was right.
對誰來說是對的？
Right for who?
制作人
金相圭
當心
Heads up.
柯迪羅上尉，我們是特工瑞特和摩根
Captain Cordero, agents Ritter and Morgan.
我們在追捕一個今早從CIA逃走的
We're in pursuit of a dangerous fugitive who escaped CIA custody
危險逃犯…傑克·鮑爾
earlier today... Jack Bauer.
制 作 人
伊恩·史密斯
他進了大使館
And he's somewhere in this embassy.
我現在的首要任務
Well, my priority right now
是保護大使館，CIA的事情先放一放
is to secure this building. CIA business will have to wait.
上尉，鮑爾就是
Captain, Bauer's the reason
這一切的罪魁禍首，他開槍打傷兩名抗議者
that all of this happened...He shot two protestors
监 制
布莱恩·格雷泽
煽動抗議人群，趁亂進入大使館
to incite the crowd and cover his entrance into the embassy.
你確定？
You're sure about that?
监 制
基弗·萨瑟兰
我們看到他開的槍
We saw him do it.
我們有理由相信他是
We have reason to believe that he's here
為無人機操作員坦納中尉而來
for lieutenant Tanner, the drone pilot
我們得馬上去找他
and we need to get to him right now
否則天知道他會做什麼
or God knows what he's gonna do in there.
跟我來
With me.
洛佩茲
Lopez
奧斯伯恩，帶上人跟我走
Osborn, your men, let's go.
讓我跟他通話
Patch me in.
监 制
强·卡萨
大卫·弗瑞
监 制
罗伯特·科克伦
坦納中尉
Lieutenant Tanner
是我
Yeah.
有什麼事嗎？
Can I help you?
先生
Sir.
监 制
曼尼·科托
我是外交安全部門的
Diplomatic security.
我奉命前來轉移你和坦納中尉
I have orders to move you and lieutenant Tanner.
我沒接到通知
I wasn't informed about this.
現在外面大亂
Security's just been breached.
外面有很多抗議者
We have protestors in the building.
如果你不聽從我的命令，我無法保證
Sir, if you don't follow me now, I cannot guarantee
你和犯人的安全
the safety of you or the prisoner.
請稍等
You stay right there.
监 制
伊万·卡茨
別怕
Don't be afraid.
我是傑克·鮑爾
My name is Jack Bauer.
我知道你的無人機是被劫持了
I know your drone was hijacked.
监 制
霍华德·高登
你知道我是無辜的？
You know I'm innocent?
编 剧
乔尔·苏尔诺
罗伯特·科克伦
是的，我知道
Yes, I do.
控制你無人機的技術
The technology that was used
將被人用在
to control your drone is gonna be used
编 剧
帕特里克·萨默维尔
今天針對平民的大規模恐怖襲擊
in a massive terrorist attack against civilians later today.
导 演
刁毓能
我唯一能阻止恐怖襲擊發生的辦法
The only way that I can stop that attack from happening
來自於你的飛行密匙
is from the data from your flight key.
中尉，求你了
Lieutenant, please
飛行密匙在哪？
where are they holding it?
等等，我怎麼知道該不該信你？
Wait, how do I know whether or not to believe you?
孩子，現在的重點是我相信你
Son,right now the point is that I believe you.
在我看來
From everything that I can see
沒有其他人相信你
no one else does.
你想洗脫罪名的話
You want your name cleared.
我是你唯一的機會
I'm your only shot.
在德諾沃上尉身上
It's on captain Denovo.
很好
Okay.
傑克，摩根和她的搭檔
Jack, agent Morgan and her partner
帶著陸戰隊的人向你的方向去了
they're heading your way with marine backup.
飛行密匙拿到了
Got the flight key.
快走，傑克，他們到二樓了
Get out of there, Jack. They're on your floor.
謝謝你，中尉
Thank you, lieutenant.
你會沒事的
You're gonna be fine.
克羅伊，指條路讓我出去
Chloe, get me out of here.
到走廊盡頭，左轉
The end of the hallway, take a left
應該能通向後方的樓梯間
That should lead you to a rear stairwell.
馬上叫醫護人員過來
Let's get a medic up here right away.
是柯迪羅隊長
This is captain Cordero.
給我進入217房的權限
Get me a keypad override on 217.
有人受傷，房間安全
Casualty down. Room is clear.
他跑了
He's gone.
鮑爾來過
Bauer was here.
說吧，他做了什麼
All right, what did he do and what
拿了什麼？
did he take?
無可奉告
I have nothing to say to you.
他拿了坦納的飛行密鑰
He took Tanner's flight key.
穿著
And he was wearing
大使館的保安夾克
an embassy security jacket
持有通行證
and he has a pass.
準備行動，我需要
Prepare to move. I want an override
最高安全權限
on all security passes.
立刻鎖死所有門和鍵盤鎖
Lock down every door and keypad now.
一路通到地下室，傑克
Go all the way down to the basement, Jack.
找到通向儲存室的門
A door leads to the storage area.
從那就能回到街面
From there, you'll have access to the street level.
瞭解
I got it.
好，我到了
Okay, I'm there.
快點
Come on.
該死
Damn it.
全部封鎖了，通行證失效
Everything's locked down. The key's useless.
找別的出路
Find me another way out.
傑克，好像沒別的路了
Jack, I don't see another way.
他們派了更多士兵來抓你，他們無處不在
They've got more marines joining the search for you. They're everywhere.
等等，等等
Hold on, hold on.
美國大使館都有自己的通訊屏蔽間
Every U.S. embassy has its own shielded communication room.
我能利用他們系統，上載飛行密匙裏的數據
I can use their system to upload the data from the flight key.
這無助於你逃脫大使館，傑克
That's not gonna help you get out of the embassy, Jack.
我知道，幫我找到通訊室就行
I know. Just find me the comms room.
可以，但你還不明白麼
Okay, but I don't think you understand.
你逃不掉的
You're not getting out of there.
一切結束了
It's over.
他們會讓你去蹲監獄
They're gonna put you in prison.
傑克！
Jack!
耶茨重寫的裝置已經
Yates' override device is officially interfaced
與我們系統匹配，現在我們就只需
with our system. All we need to do now
運行其中的軟體
is get its software talking to ours.
要多久？
How long?
我要逐個檢查這十個
Well, I need to check each of the ten guidance modules
引導組件
separately.
到底多久？
How long?
納維德能在一小時內
Naveed will be able to take control
控制並啟用無人機
and pilot the drones in less than an hour.
哦，我真想你
Oh, I missed you.
我沒發瘋，因為我知道一切結束後
But it kept me sane knowing that when all this is over
我們就有時間，來做錯過的事
We'll have time for everything we've put on hold.
旅行
Travel
組建家庭
Have a family.
聽起來不錯，但這還是不能改變我的感受
Sounds wonderful, but it doesn't change how I feel.
你還有顧慮
You have doubts.
我能理解
I understand.
但你別無選擇
But you don't have a choice.
倘若你拒絕了，知道我媽
Do you realize what my mother will do to you
會怎麼對你麼？
if you refuse?
我不會給她機會下手的
I'm not gonna give her the chance.
你在說些什麼？
What are you talking about?
走吧
Leaving.
我們一起走
You and I, together.
少開玩笑了
You can't be serious.
就算我同意，也不可能走
Even if I agreed, it's impossible.
我媽有手下監控進出…我們連正門
My mother's people watch who comes and goes... We wouldn't get past
都出不去
the front door.
亞瑟爾每天在五點和五點半之間
Yasir makes a supply run every other day
運送物資
between 5:00 and 5:30.
一小時後才回
He's due for one later.
這段時間，沒人看管後門
No one watches the back gate while he's gone.
但後門是鎖的
But that gate is locked.
我有鑰匙
I have keys.
路邊有輛車停著
And a car parked down the road.
你是下決心要走
You've made up your mind.
都計劃好了
You've planned this.
我本可以一周前就走
I could have left a week ago
但我在等你
but I waited for you.
納維德
Naveed
我愛你，所以求求你
I love you, so please
求你做完這件事
please just go through with this
我們就能遠走高飛
and then we can leave
不用再受我媽的擺佈了
and we never have to be part of my mother's plans again.
你確信她會放你走？
You believe she'll let you go?
真信過？
Ever?
我很想與你共度餘生
I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
但今天，只要亞瑟爾
But I'm leaving today
一離開,我就要走了
as soon as yasir goes on his run.
你這是讓我進退兩難
You're putting me in a terrible position.
我知道，對不起
I know. And I'm sorry.
但你還是要做出抉擇
But you need to make a choice.
我，或是你媽
Your mother or me.
好吧
Okay.
我跟你走
I'll come.
你還好吧？
You okay?
還好吧？
Yeah?
嗯
Mmm.
突發狀況，大使館已被封鎖
We got a flash that the embassy's on lockdown.
發生什麼了？
What's going on there?
鮑爾過來了，槍擊了兩名抗議者
Bauer's here. He shot two protesters
並且強行闖入大使館
and forced his way inside the embassy
去找了坦納
and he got to Tanner.
他們是串通的？
So they are working together.
不知道這次還講不講得通
I'm not sure if that makes sense anymore.
這次他有機會，但沒打算救他出去
He didn't try to release Tanner when he had the chance.
他只拿了飛行密匙
He just took his flight key.
二層安全，我們下去
Level two clear. We're moving down.
這麼說，鮑爾是要坦納的無人機數據，為什麼？
So Bauer wanted the flight data to Tanner's drone. Why?
抓到鮑爾後，我們會問的
We're gonna ask Bauer when we get to him
但現在，他還藏在大使館的某處
but right now he's still somewhere inside the embassy
我們正在逐層搜索
and we're going floor by floor.
好，隨時保持聯繫
All right, keep me posted.
你左邊是防火安全門
There's a fire door on your left.
右邊就是通訊室
Comm room is coming up on your right.
看到了
Got 'em.
別回頭，開門
Don't turn around. Open the door.
進去，每個人
Get inside. Everybody
都站起來！快點！
on their feet now! Now!
慢慢挪到牆角
Move slowly towards the corner.
坐下去，別亂動
Sit on the ground and don't move.
克羅伊，我進來了
Chloe, I'm inside.
你需要一台連接通用串行總線的終端機
You need a terminal with a USB port.
就在這
I got it.
正在插入飛行密鑰
Plugging in the flight key now.
好，運行命令行
Okay, go to a command line
開啟T型網絡
open a t-net window.
我給你個安全的IP地址
I'll give you a secure IP address.
等一下
Hold on.
好了
Okay.
地址是：2
It's 2.
718.
281.
828.
上传进度
能用，他們追到哪了？
Done. How close are the marines?
很近了，傑克
Really close, Jack.
克羅伊，如果我有什麼不測
Chloe, no matter what happens to me
上传进度
你要把證據交給海勒總統，好麼？
you get this evidence to president Heller, okay?
好
Okay.
向我保證
Give me your word.
我保證過了，傑克
You have my word, Jack.
传输终止
怎麼回事？
What the hell was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
飛行密匙的數據加過密
The data on the flight key is encrypted.
傳輸之前
It needs to be unlocked
要先從終端解鎖
from his end before it can be transmitted.
那要怎麼辦？
What do we need to do then?
呃
Well
我們先給你發送
We could send you
解碼程序軟體，然後你再
A software program that will decrypt it and then
上載給我們
upload it to us.
你可以進行接收了
You should be receiving that now.
媽的，要多長時間？
Son of a bitch. How long is this gonna take?
我不知道，那要看
I've no idea. It depends on the level
加密級別了
of encryption they've used.
快點，快點
Come on. Come on.
傑克，他們到走廊了
Jack, they're in the corridor,
就在門口，沒時間了
right outside. You have to buy more time.
他們從哪個方向來的？
Which direction are they coming from?
從你左邊那個拐角處
Rounding the corner on your left.
你能看清這些陸戰隊員穿沒穿
Can you see if the marines are wearing
防彈衣嗎？
body armor?
我看著像是穿了
Looks like it to me.
你，穿黑衣服的那個，你叫什麼？
You, in the black jacket, what's your name?
詹妮
Jenny.
詹妮，你慢慢地
Jenny, slowly
到我這邊來
come towards me.
聽我命令，我讓你開門時就開門
I need you to open the door on my command.
就是這樣，詹妮，你做得很好
It's all right, Jenny, you're doing great.
輸入密碼
Just put in the code.
克羅伊，他們到哪裏了？
Chloe, where are they?
就在你面前，傑克
They're on you, Jack.
開門
Open the door now.
我有人質！全都退後！關門！
I've got hostages! Stay back! Close the door now!
怎樣？
Well?
來杯茶嗎？
A cup of tea?
嗯，好
Yes, please.
你在努力組織語言想要我告訴我一些事情
You're trying to find the right words to tell me something.
一些不好的事情
A problem.
有那麼明顯嗎？
It's that obvious?
是納維德，對吧？
It's Naveed, isn't it?
他說他沒有辦法做這件事
He says he can't go through with it.
駕駛那些無人機
Pilot the drones.
他計劃逃走，然後我說我願意跟他一起走
He has a plan to leave, and I've said I'll go with him.
我這麼說只是為了爭取時間讓我們想對策
Just to give us time to work out what to do.
請不要傷害他
Please don't hurt him.
那你認為一次嚴厲的訓話
And do you think a stern talking-to
就能讓他改變主意嗎？
will get him to change his mind?
不能，可是
No, but
可是什麼？
But what?
我愛他
I love him.
這樣的話，他可真是幸運
And he's very lucky that is the case.
為了不讓
This family
某些人某些事成為阻撓
has worked too hard for too long
這個家已經苦苦經營了很多年
to let anything or anyone get in its way.
也許你覺得納維德是你的丈夫
Naveed may be your husband
但是你要明白，為了讓他
But you must understand, I will do
駕駛那些無人機，必要時我會不擇手段
whatever's necessary to get him to pilot those drones.
我誠願語言能挽救
I wish there were words
我們雙方今天失去的
that could bring back the fathers and husbands
人父和人夫
lost today on both our sides.
我只希望你們能聽我說完
My hope is that you will hear me out.
這樣我們或許可以找到一種方式
So that we might find a way
攜手
to move forward
面對未來
together.
面對未來的第一件事
Moving forward together
就是要認清我們所面臨的威脅
begins with an understanding of the threat that we face
那是一個決絕的敵人
a determined enemy
他誓要毀掉我們的生活
sworn to destroy our way of life.
我們的人民，在針對城市和公共建設的
Thousands of our citizens killed in attacks
襲擊中慘遭殺害
against our cities and our infrastructure.
我們的人民，在阿富汗和伊拉克戰場上
Thousands killed on the battlefields of Afghanistan
為國捐軀
and Iraq.
但是勝利終將屬於我們
But we can prevail.
我是馬克·布德羅
This is Mark Boudreau.
先生，我是分局局長納瓦羅
Sir, this is head of station navarro
打電話來告知您鮑爾事件的進展
calling to give you an update on the Bauer situation.
你抓住他了？
Have you apprehended him?
確切來說沒有，先生
Not exactly, sir.
鮑爾被困在美國大使館內部
Bauer has barricaded himself inside the communications room
通訊室裏，而且
at the American embassy. And
他手上有人質
He's taken hostages.
什麼？怎麼回事？
What? Why?
我們還在努力搞清事情的來龍去脈
We're still trying to get a complete picture
但是您曾明確指示
but you gave me specific instructions
鮑爾出現在這裏的事要保密
to keep Bauer's presence here in London a secret.
我只是想提醒您
And I just wanted to give you
這事兒已經不再是秘密了
advanced warning that that will no longer be possible
明擺的
obviously.
特工納瓦羅
Agent navarro
之後我們再說我對你的表現
we'll talk about my disappointment
有多失望
with your performance later.
但是現在，告訴我
But now, tell me
陸戰隊是否已經把局面控制住？
have the marines taken control of the situation?
已經控制住了，先生，而且我認為
Yes, sir, they have. And I assume it's only a matter
這件事遲早
of time before they send this up the chain of command
會反映上去驚動總統
to the president.
總統要從我的口中知道這件事
The president needs to hear it from me.
我要你把你知道的全都告訴我
I need to know what you know.
解密程序已經啟動運行了
Okay, the decryption program is up and running.
但很慢
But slowly.
我這裏能看到，稍等，傑克
I can see that. Hang on a second, Jack.
你編的這個軟體，你能讓它加快速度嗎？
You wrote this. Can you speed it up?
不行，問題出在他那邊，你看
No, trouble's on his end. Look.
他使用的終端
The terminal he's using only has
只有一個單核處理器
a single-core processor.
真的嗎？
Really?
還是你這麼說只是為了再坑傑克一次？
Or are you just saying that to screw over Jack again?
我怎麼知道你說的是不是實話？
How do I know you're telling the truth?
我做這件事是為了你，不是為了他
I'm doing this for you, not for him.
傑克，我們這邊也沒有辦法
Jack, there's nothing we can do.
按照當前速率，破譯數據
At this rate, it'll take 20 to 30 minutes
並傳輸給我們要20到30分鐘
to get the data unlocked and transmitted to us.
我是傑克·鮑爾，哪位？
This is Jack Bauer. Who am I talking to?
我是凱文·科迪羅上尉，鮑爾先生
My name is captain Kevin Cordero. Mr. Bauer
我相信我們都想在不傷及任何人性命的情況下
I'm sure we'd both like to find a way to end this situation
解決這件事，不論是你的性命還是人質的
without loss of life. Yours or the hostages.
我希望我們能合作
I'd like us to work together
上尉，現在的情況很簡單，我有三名人質
Captain, the situation is simple. I have three hostages.
讓你的人退後就沒人會受到傷害
Keep your men back and no one gets harmed.
你敢對這房間採取任何行動
Make a move on this room
我就把他們全部殺掉
and I kill all three of them.
我說清楚了嗎？
Are we clear?
清楚明白
Loud and clear.
我們進去，我不會再讓那個混蛋有機會
We go in, I'm not giving that son of a bitch a chance
開槍打我的人
to fire at my men again.
我只是需要讓他們有所忌憚
I need them to take me seriously.
我無意傷害你們任何人
I have no intention of hurting any of you.
我知道你們很難受
I understand how difficult this is.
可是，請盡量
Please, just try
保持冷靜
and stay calm.
我們還沒有機會自我介紹過
We didn't get to introduce ourselves earlier.
我是特工裏特，中情局的
I'm agent Ritter, CIA.
這位是特工摩根
This is agent Morgan.
我們來這裏並不是要
Look, we're not here to prove
指控你什麼事，中尉
any kind of case against you, lieutenant.
我們只是想跟你聊聊鮑爾的事
We just want to talk to you about Bauer.
說到鮑爾，你得明白
And speaking of Bauer, you should know
他就在我們樓下三層
that right now he's three levels below us
被陸戰隊員團團圍住
completely surrounded by marines.
所以你要是想讓他給你幫助，趁早死了這條心
So any help you were expecting from him, don't.
跟我們說說吧，中尉
Talk to us, lieutenant.
有什麼意義呢？
What's the point?
一整天了，除了鮑爾沒人相信我說的話
No one but Bauer's believed a word I've said all day.
你和鮑爾是什麼關係？
What is your relationship with Bauer?
我們今天才認識
I just met him today.
你覺得我們會相信嗎？
You expect us to believe that?
如果你
Look, if you
此前不認識鮑爾的話，那麼
Didn't know Bauer before this, then, um,
他為什麼費這麼大勁找到你呢？
why did he go to so much trouble to find you?
他說他知道我並沒有殺那些士兵
He said he knew I didn't kill all those soldiers
他知道我的無人機是被劫持了
that my drone was hijacked
而且有人要用同樣的方法
and someone was gonna use the same technology
發起一場全面的襲擊
to launch a full-scale attack.
那他要你的飛行密匙做什麼？
So why did he need your flight key?
他說那個能幫助他證明發生了什麼事
He said it could help him prove what happened.
阻止這次襲擊
And stop the attack.
好的，謝謝你，中尉
Okay, thank you, lieutenant.
我們應該再逼緊一點的
We should've pushed him harder.
我覺得他知道的都已經告訴我們了
I think he told us everything he knows.
根本沒說多少
Which wasn't much.
但是你…你相信那個故事？
But you did... You're buying that story?
當鮑爾在摩天大樓那裏制住我的時候
Look, when Bauer cornered me in the tower block, he said
他說他來倫敦是為了阻止一場針對海勒總統的襲擊
that he was in London to stop an attack on president Heller.
什麼意思？
Meaning what?
你相信他跟坦納說的那些鬼話？
You believe what he told Tanner?
就算這件事根本就是
Even though there's not a single piece
空口無憑？
of evidence to support it?
我不是這個意思
That's not what I'm saying.
我的意思是，哪怕有一丁點
What I'm saying is that if there's even a chance
發生某種襲擊的可能
that there's gonna be some kind of an attack
我們就要弄明白這事
then we need to know about it.
我們得跟鮑爾談談
We have to talk to Bauer.
我要感謝你們，代表我自己
I would like to thank you, on behalf of myself
和我的國家，感謝能有這次機會
and my country, for this opportunity
讓我們向將英美兩大國
to express our gratitude and appreciation
維繫在一起的特殊關係
for the special relationship
表達感激之情
that binds our two great nations together.
天祐聯合王國
God bless the United Kingdom.
天祐美利堅合眾國
And God bless the United States of America.
謝謝各位
Thank you.
聽到了嗎？
You hear that?
您講得太棒了
You were fantastic.
或許是他們太有禮貌
Or they're extremely polite.
講得很棒
It was perfect.
我能單獨跟您聊聊嗎？
Can I talk to you privately?
謝謝
Thank you.
怎麼了？
What's going on?
大使館出狀況了，先生
There's a situation at the embassy, sir.
約半小時前，抗議者
Protesters broke through the gates
闖過了關卡，陸戰隊已經
about a half an hour ago. The marines have
重設了安全邊界，但是
reestablished a perimeter, but
有人劫持人質
It's turned into a hostage situation.
人質？
Hostages?
誰劫持人質？
Who's taken hostages?
傑克·鮑爾
Jack Bauer.
傑克？
Jack?
他開槍衝進抗議人群
He fired into the crowd of protesters,
擊中兩名海軍士兵，還威脅
shot two marines, and is threatening
要殺死他挾持的大使館員工
to kill the embassy employees he's holding.
他到底為什麼要這麼做？
Why in God's name would Jack do this?
我只知道中情局
All I know is, the CIA
幾小時前在任務中擒住了他
picked him up several hours ago on an operation
但他逃脫了
but he escaped custody.
什麼…你在那時就得知此事了？
What... is that when you found out about this?
是的
It was.
令人擔心的是，他來了倫敦
The fear was that he was in London
因為您來訪問，我正為您
for your visit. I was in the process of gathering
收集所有信息的時候
all the facts together for you
他又重新出現在大使館
when he resurfaced at the embassy.
現場目前是什麼情況？
What's the situation on the ground right now?
據科伯恩將軍所說
According to general Coburn,
突擊隊已經準備進入
the assault team is ready to go in.
只等您的命令
They're just waiting for your go-ahead.
你的意思是他們可以殺了傑克
So they can kill him. That's what you're saying.
目前還不是既成事實
It's not a fait accompli.
在我跟他談話之前
I'm not making any decisions
我不會做任何決定
till I talk to him.
跟鮑爾談話嗎，先生？我…我不確定這
To Bauer, sir? I... I'm not sure that
是的，去安排吧，馬克
Yeah. Make it happen, Mark.
是，閣下
Yes, sir.
我偷偷查過了
I've checked, without being obvious.
亞瑟爾逃了，我們可以走了
Yasir's going on his run, we're good to go.
你居然告訴她
You told her.
她也不願意
It wasn't easy for her.
我女兒非常愛你
My daughter loves you very much.
出爾反爾會壞了你的名聲，納維德
Trying to back out is a stain on your honor, Naveed.
我給你一次機會
I will give you one chance
彌補錯誤
to rectify that.
向我保證你會操縱無人機
Tell me you'll pilot the drones.
我不會傷及無辜
I won't murder innocents.
沒人是無辜的
There are no innocents.
因為他們選了海勒和戴維斯
Not when they elect murderers
這樣的兇手
and collaborators like
和通敵叛徒來領導他們
Heller and Davies to lead them.
一派胡言
That's nonsense.
該有人站出來說實話了
And it's time someone here stood up and said it.
這樣不對
This is wrong.
如果西蒙娜能擺脫你
And if Simone ever got free of you
她也會這樣認為
she'd see that, too.
這不是道德
This isn't conscience.
這是懦弱
This is cowardice.
如果我丈夫還活著，他會非常討厭你
If my husband were alive, he'd be sickened by you.
他所犧牲的一切
Everything he sacrificed
他所維護的一切
everything he stood for.
你必須操縱無人機
You will pilot the drones.
我拒絕
I will not.
不管你怎樣折磨我
No matter what you do to me.
我發誓
I swear.
我相信你
I believe you.
西蒙娜
Simone.
嗯？
Mum?
請過來
Come here, please.
噢，噢！
Oh, oh!
她的左手
Her left hand.
不要，不要！
No. No!
啊！你幹什麼？
Aah! What are you doing?
必須如此，親愛的
Whatever's necessary, my love.
不要！
No!
動手吧
Do it.
不要！
No!
快停下！
Stop this!
只有你能讓我停下，納維德
Only you can do that, Naveed.
再來
Again.
好吧，我同意！
Okay, all right!
我同意，快住手，求你住手
All right, just stop. Stop. No, no, please!
你會做必須之事？
You'll do what's necessary?
我會
Yeah.
我會，只要別傷害她，求你
Yeah, just stop hurting her, please.
柯迪羅隊長，我們只需跟鮑爾談談
Captain Cordero, we just need to talk to Bauer.
不行，他現在很不穩定
Not when he's that unstable.
我們不知道什麼事會激怒他，人命關天
We don't know what could set him off. Lives are at stake here.
如果鮑爾跟坦納中尉說的是真的
If what Bauer told lieutenant Tanner is true
會有更多人有危險
then many more lives will be at stake.
我們只需知道他說的話是不是真的
We just need to know if there's any truth to it.
我不會允許任何不穩定因素
I'm not introducing any other variables into this equation.
談話就此結束
This conversation is over.
好了，可以從這個天花板通風口
All right, this ceiling vent here
直接進入，但問題是我們每次只能
gives us direct access, but the problem there is we have to
放下去一個人
drop men down into the room one at a time.
要進去，我們得一起進去，明白嗎？
We go in, we go in in numbers, understood?
我知道你不想聽這話
Look, I know you don't want to hear this, but
他說得對
he's probably right.
鮑爾開槍打在兩個海軍
Bauer shot those two marines
防彈背心的中間，他明知道
square in the middle of their vests, where he knew
子彈打不透那裏
the rounds wouldn't penetrate.
這才是掌控局面的人
That's what I call someone in control.
你在幹嘛？
What are you doing?
繞過柯迪羅
Going over Cordero's head.
喬丹
Jordan
納瓦羅在你旁邊嗎？
you with navarro?
長官
Sir.
給您開免提，是凱特
Putting you on speaker. It's Kate.
你審問坦納了嗎？
Were you able to debrief Tanner?
是的，而且鮑爾告訴坦納說他有消息
Yeah, we did, and Bauer told Tanner that he has intel
馬上會發生襲擊事件，來自我國的無人機
about an imminent attack, using our own drones, but
但負責這裏的上尉拒絕
the marine captain here in charge is refusing
讓我們與鮑爾談話，所以我們證實
to let us talk to Bauer so we can get a confirmation on this.
這是軍事行動，我無法命令他
It's a military operation, I can't overrule him.
但您認識的人能做到，您一直跟
But you know people who can. You've been speaking
總統的辦公廳主管有聯繫
with the president's chief of staff.
現在最不滿意的就是他
Who isn't very happy with us right now
我們弄丟了鮑爾
for losing Bauer in the first place.
先生，總統需要知道鮑爾說的事
Sir, the president needs to know about Bauer's claims.
鮑爾會有機會直接跟總統對話
Bauer will get his chance to address the president directly.
什麼？
What?
海勒總統隨時會親自聯繫鮑爾
President Heller will be reaching out to Bauer
嘗試是否能讓他投降
personally at any moment to see if he can get him to surrender.
那你能讓我們也聽到電話嗎？
Well, can you patch us in to the call?
我會讓喬丹
I'll have Jordan
把你和埃裏克綁定的
tie you and Erik in.
會不會鮑爾真的是
Is it possible that Bauer really
在試圖阻止襲擊？
is trying to stop an attack?
你說的這個人
You're talking about the man who
今早剛熟練地踐踏了
practically laid waste to my
我的基地
station this morning.
只是想到
Just thinking
如果我們聽取了凱特之前說的話
If we'd listened to what Kate said before
我們本不會失去鮑爾
we wouldn't have lost Bauer in the first place.
你什麼意思？
What are you saying?
無視她的意見會造成損失
That it doesn't pay to dismiss what she says.
我沒有無視她的意見，只是要保持客觀立場
I'm not dismissing her. I'm remaining objective.
很明顯，你就沒有保持住
Which is something you're not doing, for obvious reasons.
我不是瞎子，喬丹
I'm not blind, Jordan.
你對她的好感蒙蔽了你的判斷力
You're letting your feelings for her cloud your judgment.
是，長官
Yes, sir.
凱特並非絕對可靠
Kate's not infallible.
還記得她在她丈夫的事上錯得多離譜吧
Remember how wrong she was about her husband.
有些錯誤就是
Some mistakes you just
無法挽回
can't recover from.
總統打來電話了
The call from the president's coming through.
上传进度
上尉，我覺得我們已經達成共識了
Captain, I thought we had an understanding.
傑克？
Jack?
是我
It's me.
總統先生
Mr. president.
說實話，傑克
To be honest with you, Jack,
我從沒想過還能再聽到你的聲音
I never thought I'd have to hear your voice again.
我更喜歡那樣
I liked it that way.
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
有人告訴我你剛擊倒了兩個人
I'm told you just shot two people
就在大使館門外
out in front of the embassy.
我根本沒傷到他們，先生
I barely grazed them, sir.
你怎麼知道？
How do you know that?
因為是我開的槍
Because I pulled the trigger.
而且你還劫持了人質
And now you're holding hostages.
凱特
Kate
你和埃裏克聽到電話了嗎？
are you and Erik getting this?
聽到了
Yeah.
我相信你知道我們必須要做決定
I'm sure you know that there's some decisions to be made here
但在此之前
but before we do that
我想試試看你我二人能否解決問題，所以告訴我
I would like to see if you and I could resolve this. So tell me
你為何而來，你想幹什麼？
why are you here and what do you want?
總統先生，我來這是因為我相信
Mr. president, I'm here because I believe
美國無人機即將被用於
the U.S. drone fleet is vulnerable and will be used
今日的一起恐怖襲擊
in a terrorist attack later today.
解釋一下，傑克
Explain that, Jack.
一個叫德裏克·耶茨的黑客
A hacker by the name of Derek yates
製造了一台遙控裝置，可以
created an override device which can
控制多達十架美國無人機
take control of as many as ten U.S. drones.
我相信正是此人挾持了
I believe he was the one who hijacked
坦納中尉的無人機，並用來試飛
lieutenant Tanner's drone and used it as a test flight
向他的買家證明裝置有效
to prove to his buyers that the device worked.
之後他很快就被殺害了
Shortly after that I found him murdered.
我相信現在此裝置在
Now I believe that the device is in the hands
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲手上，她是恐怖分子
of Margot Al-Harazi, a known terrorist.
總統先生，我向您保證
Mr. president, I promise you:
有這個裝置，她絕不會手下留情的
She will use this device without mercy.
你在那個房間幹什麼呢，傑克？
What are you doing in that room, Jack?
上傳從坦納中尉的飛行密匙中獲得的數據
Uploading data from lieutenant Tanner's flight key.
與我合作的人相信他們能用這些數據
I'm working with people who believe they can use this data
證明裝置的存在
to prove that the device exists.
我們的計劃是，一旦取得證據
Our plan was, as soon as we had the evidence
我就馬上自首，將證據呈現給您
I would turn myself in and present it to you.
跟你合作的這些人是誰？
Who are these people you're working with?
總統先生，我不能說
Mr. president, I can't say.
先生，我需要15分鐘
Sir, I need 15 minutes.
只要15分鐘，我就能提供你需要的證據
15 minutes and I can get you the evidence you need.
我保證我會交出自己，不造成任何傷亡
And I promise I will hand myself over without incident.
你為什麼不一開始就來找我，傑克？
Why didn't you come to me first, Jack?
無意冒犯，總統先生
With all due respect, Mr. president
正是您的國務院判定我是恐怖分子
it was your state department that labeled me a terrorist
並通緝我的
and made me a wanted man.
一個根本沒有機會
A man who was never even offered an opportunity
為自己辯解的人，而且，閣下
to tell his side of the story. Which, by the way, sir
我覺得我是有功勞的
I felt I had earned.
所以，不會，我不會安然地
So, no, I did not feel comfortable going to talk
跟你們談，我知道我只能
to your people. I knew that I had to either
帶著裝置來
arrive with the device
或者裝置存在的證據
or evidence that the device existed.
唯其如此，他們才會相信
That would be the only way they would believe me.
唯其如此，你才會相信
The only way you would believe me.
好吧，傑克
All right, Jack.
別掛電話，我等會跟你說
Stay by this phone. I'll get back to you.
閣下
Sir
無論我們有什麼分歧
Whatever differences we had
我從未騙過你
I never lied to you.
我對你只說實話
I always told you the truth.
我現在就在說實話，我建議你聽進去
I'm telling you the truth now, and I suggest you believe it.
我聽到了，傑克
I hear you, Jack.
克羅伊，你聽到了嗎？
Chloe, did you get that?
我們時間不多了
We don't have much time.
他有可能對嗎？坦納中尉的無人機有可能
Could he be right? Could this lieutenant Tanner's drone
被劫持了嗎？
have been hijacked?
我們分析過坦納飛行密匙上的數據
We analyzed the data on Tanner's flight key
沒有線索，而且，坦白說
and found no evidence of that. And, frankly
無人機的網絡被設計成避免這種情況的
the drone network was designed to avoid exactly that scenario.
沒什麼是不可能的
Well, nothing's impossible.
我是說
I mean
問題在於，為什麼傑克要編造這些？
the real question is, why would Jack make this up?
來掩蓋他的真實意圖
To cover up what he's really doing.
今天早些時候，他幫助前同事
Earlier today, he broke a former associate
逃脫了中情局的關押，克羅伊·奧布賴恩
out of CIA custody. Chloe O'Brian.
克羅伊？
Chloe?
她是艾德裏安·克羅斯黑客組織
She's a member of Adrian cross' group
的成員
open cell.
他們「解放」了3萬份政府文件
Who "liberated" 30,000 secret government documents
將前線特工的生命置於險境
endangering the lives of agents on the ground.
他們是傑克的人
They are Jack's people.
恐怖威脅只是幌子
The terrorist threat is a cover
為他爭取時間上傳數據
to buy him time to upload data
給黑客組織，他要求15分鐘
to open cell. He asked for only 15 minutes.
我們猶豫的每一秒都關係人命
Every second we hesitate could cost lives.
為什麼不阻止上傳？
Why don't we just kill the upload?
不行，閣下，他在獨立的
We can't, sir. He's in a secure
通訊室了
comms room.
他故意挑選的
It's why he chose it.
萬一傑克說的襲擊是真的呢？
And what if Jack is telling the truth on this attack?
你願意冒險嗎？
Are you willing to take that risk?
或者冒險讓黑客組織
Or risk even more
搞更多破壞
damage from open cell.
他是被認定的恐怖分子
He's a designated terrorist.
我們不和恐怖分子談判
We don't negotiate with terrorists.
恕我直言，閣下，這個決策很明確
With all due respect, sir, this is a clear call.
或許你覺得明確，馬克
Maybe a clear call for you, Mark.
我和奧德莉不覺得
Not so for Audrey and I.
我們認識傑克·鮑爾
We know Jack Bauer.
你不認識
You don't.
你說得對
You're right.
我只看到了他出現時造成的破壞
All I've ever seen is the damage he leaves in his wake.
我們別忘了
Let's not forget
他4年前的殺戮盛宴
the killing spree that he went on four years ago
差點殺死俄羅斯總統
when he nearly assassinated the Russian president.
然後他逃到國外
And then he fled the country
因為他不想在監獄度過餘生
because he didn't want to spend the rest of his life in jail.
他已經不是你認識的那個人了
This is not the same man you once knew.
叫士兵們準備好就動手
Tell the marines to go in when they're ready.
我給你看點東西
I need to show you something.
這些是幾年前的無人機攻擊
These drone attacks were from a few years ago.
最新的無人機裝載更大威力的導彈
The latest drones carry even more powerful missiles.
你不必說服我
You hardly need to convince me
政府不應用無人機殺害平民
that governments shouldn't be killing civilians by remote control.
想像這些發生在倫敦這裏
Imagine this happening here in London
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲掌控了10架無人機
when Margot Al-Harazi gets control of ten drones.
想想那些要死的人
Think of the people that will die.
我不懂你的意思
I'm not really seeing your point.
我在幫忙
I am trying to help.
我的意思是
My point
軍方認為傑克是個威脅
is that the marines think that Jack is a threat.
他們殺了他
They're going to kill him
阻止這些的機會也沒了
along with any chance we have of stopping this.
如果你能想出更好的辦法說服政府
So if you can think of a better way to convince the government
傑克說的是實話，現在就告訴我
that Jack is telling the truth, then tell me now.
求你
Please.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我也很抱歉
Me, too.
你和鮑爾怎麼回事？
What is it with you and Bauer?
你為什麼放不下他？
Why can't you just let him go?
鮑爾已經向兩名士兵開槍
Bauer's already shot two marines, so
現在是一觸即發
this is a hair-trigger situation.
你們都清楚他很危險
You even get a sense that he is a threat, and
你們的任何行動我都會支持
I will back up whatever decision you have to make in there.
明白嗎？
Understood?
是，長官
Yes, sir.
有機會開槍
The instant you get a shot
就幹掉鮑爾，明白嗎？
take Bauer out. Clear?
今天鮑爾告訴總統的話解釋了
What Bauer told the president today explains everything
他的所有作為
that he's done.
追蹤耶茨和飛行密匙
Going after yates and the flight key.
他為什麼要救出克羅伊·奧布賴恩？
Why did he break Chloe O'Brian out?
他說耶茨是黑客，也許她認識他
He said yates was a hacker. Maybe she knew him.
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲的信息已經找到
Margot Al-Harazi's details check out.
玛戈·阿尔哈拉兹
她據信藏在英國
She's believed to be hiding somewhere in England.
她的丈夫被無人機殺死
Her husband was killed in a drone attack.
陸戰隊在找機會幹掉鮑爾
The marines are looking for any excuse to take Bauer down
果真如此，我們就失去了
and if that happens, we're gonna lose
阻止這次襲擊的最佳機會
our best chance at stopping this attack.
凱特，我們會在全局內同步
Kate, we'll do an all-agency sync on what we know
瑪戈的信息，最新消息，一切細節
about Margot... Last-knowns, everything
以防她有所行動
just in case she does make some kind of move.
但目前只能如此
But that's all we can do right now.
總統已經發話了，明白嗎？
The president has spoken. Understood?
是的
Yes.
過來
Come here.
柯迪羅上尉說有個通風口
Captain Cordero said there was a ceiling vent
直達通訊室
that drops right down into the comms room
我敢肯定這裏是入口
and I'm pretty sure this is the entrance.
怎樣？
Yeah?
你掩護我，我要進去
You have to cover me. I'm gonna go in.
你這麼做
You do that,
鮑爾會一槍打死你
and Bauer will put a bullet in you.
也許吧，但我相信
Maybe, but I don't believe
他不是真的想殺人
that he actually wants to kill anybody.
我要嘗試讓他投降
I'm just gonna try and get him to surrender.
總統都說服不了他
Oh, he wouldn't come out for the president
你能說服他？
but he'll come out for you?
如果我說服他，我贊同他
Look, if I can convince him that I am on his side
凱特，凱特，不要
Kate. Kate, don't
我要冒這個險
It's my risk to take.
親愛的，你生氣了
Sweetheart, you're angry.
我明白，你和鮑爾有過一段
I understand. You have a history with Bauer.
不必遷就我，馬克
Don't patronize me, Mark.
我剛才只是就事論事
All I did was argue the facts in there.
是的，為了你個人的打算
Yeah, because of your personal agenda.
我可不是
I'm not the one
讓個人感情耽誤工作的人
who's letting their personal feelings get in the way.
是嗎？那你為什麼不告訴我
Oh, really? Then why didn't you tell me
傑克在倫敦，在你剛聽到消息的時候？
that Jack was in London when you first found out?
我剛才說了，我在搜集信息
Like I said, I was gathering the facts.
我不信
I don't believe that.
我告訴你，這個決策是錯誤的
I am telling you that this is the wrong call.
傑克說的是實話，這是基於我對他的瞭解
Jack is telling the truth, and that's based on me knowing him
多於這裏所有人
better than anyone else in that room.
這是我仔細斟酌後的觀點
That is my measured opinion.
萬一我對了，但願上帝保佑我們
And God help us... if I'm right.
不不不
No, no, no.
傑克，他們切斷了監控信號
No. Jack, they're cutting the cameras.
我能聽到他們在準備
I can hear them getting ready.
海勒一定下命令了
Heller must have given the order.
你必須投降，這是你唯一的機會
You need to surrender. This is your only chance.
那就前功盡棄了
No. Then all of this would have been for nothing.
我會盡量拖延他們
I'm gonna hold them off as long as I can.
直到傳輸完成
Till the transmission goes through.
傑克，他們會殺了你的
Jack, they're gonna kill you.
投降吧
Give yourself up.
傑克！
Jack!
當他們炸門，聲音會非常大
When they blow the door, it's going to sound like hell.
你們都坐著別動，會沒事的
Just stay down and keep still. You'll be safe.
我保證
I promise.
捂上耳朵
Cover your ears
低下頭
and keep your heads down.
長官？
Sir?
我們發現另外一個熱能信號接近那個房間
We're picking up another heat signature approaching the room.
給我看
Show me.
是摩根特工
It's agent Morgan.
她在試圖勸鮑爾
She's trying to get Bauer
投降，給她機會
to turn himself in. Give her that chance.
我有命令，特工，我會執行命令
I have my orders, agent. I'm executing them.
哦，先斬後奏嗎？
Yeah, shoot first, ask questions later?
把他帶走
Get him out of my sight.
是，長官，我們走吧
Yes, sir. Let's go.
聽到槍聲
We have a shot fired.
重複，有槍聲，多久？
Repeat, shot fired. How long?
60秒
60 seconds.
鮑爾，我是摩根特工！
Bauer, it's agent Morgan!
別開槍！我沒帶槍
Hold your fire! I'm unarmed.
滾開！
Back off!
我聽了你和總統的通話了
I heard your call with the president.
他可能不相信你，但我信
He may not have believed you, but I do.
我現在下來了，我重複一遍
I'm going to come down into the room now. I repeat
我沒帶槍
I am unarmed.
我可以帶你活著出去
I can get you out of here alive.
這不重要
That's not the priority.
我知道，飛行密匙重要
I know, the flight key is.
上傳還要多少時間？
How much more time do you have left on the upload?
不到5分鐘
Less than five minutes.
你沒那麼多時間了！
You don't have that much time!
士兵們馬上就會進來
Those marines are gonna come through that door
他們會殺了你
and they're gonna kill you.
但你還有選擇
But you do have another option.
你把飛行密匙給我
You can give me the flight key
我幫你完成上傳
and I can finish the upload for you
帶鑰匙出去
and get it out of here.
我為什麼要相信你？
Why the hell should I trust you?
因為我相信你
Because I really do believe you.
因為你也沒招了
And 'cause you don't have another play.
聽她的，傑克
Listen to her, Jack.
預備，長官
Ready, sir.
倒數…3
On... three
two
one.
行動
Go.
別開槍！別開槍！
Do not fire! Do not fire!
我已控制住鮑爾！
I have Bauer in my custody!
他是我的犯人，退後！
This is my prisoner. Back off!
現在中情局接管了
This is a CIA matter now.
他是我的犯人
He's in our custody.
退後
Stand down.
埃裏克，手銬給我，給納瓦羅打電話
Erik, I need your cuffs. Get Navarro on the phone
要他帶我們出去
and tell him to get us out of here.
關閉所有的通訊！
Shut down everything, all transmissions!
保護人質！
Secure the hostages!
沒事的，來吧，我們走
It's all right. Come on, let's go.
我說了，退後！退後！
I said, back off! Come on, back off.
這將是海勒總統第一次在議會演講
This will be president Heller's first address to parliament
也是最近第一位外國首腦在兩院演講
and the first foreign head of state to address a joint session
上一位是加拿大總理傑·吉爾尼克
since the Canadian Prime Minister Jay Gelnick almost two years ago.
上传中止
根據國防部的資料
According to department of defense records
飛行員克裏斯·坦納於2011年
pilot Christopher Tanner is a 2011 graduate
畢業於美國空軍學院
of the United States air force acad
我們正式上線了
We are officially online.
瞧瞧這個
Look at that.
過濾美國在歐洲的飛行無人機
Filtering for U.S. drones operating over Europe.
找出十架
Identify the ten most
靠近倫敦重裝無人機
heavily-armed drones closest to London
納維德會遙控飛行
and Naveed will take over the piloting.
對嗎？
Yes?
是的
Yes.
更多原创翻译字幕请访问
TLF论坛：http://bbs.eastgame.org
TLF中文字幕站：http://sub.eastgame.org
TLF字幕组微博：http://weibo.com/tlfsubs